

CONTACT ME AT

+39 342 884 5586

davide.guidolin11@gmail.com

https://davideguidolin.com

LANGUAGES

- English level B2
- Spanish level A2
- Italian mother tongue

SKILLS

Hard skills

- Software development: C, C++, Python, Java, Rust
- Machine Learning: PyTorch, ONNX, TensorRT
- Web development: Node.js, Java Servlets, Javascript, JQuery
- Algorithms and data structures
- Databases
- Cybersecurity

Soft skills

- Organisational skills
- Project management
- Problem solving
- Adaptability

DAVIDE GUIDOLIN

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a 23 year old student pursuing a master's degree in Artificial Intelligence Systems.

I'm an IT and AI enthusiast but I'm also interested in economics and finance.

I'm an ambitious guy and when I set a goal I work hard until I reach it. I developed this behaviour during my carrer as professional swimmer during which I became Italian youth champion thanks to the hard work. I'm a positive guy and I always tend to look at the good side of the problems.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Internship at Photoroom

Paris (France) | Apr 2023 - Sep 2023

- I worked in the ML team to explore, implement and optimize new deep learning solutions for a new feature in the PhotoRoom application
- I learned more about ML development for production and about the optimization of ML models using ONNX and TensorRT

Internship at Amazon AWS

Asti (Turin, Italy) | Aug 2021 - Oct 2021

- I worked in the NICE DCV team and I had to implement the gamepads support for the NICE DCV desktop remotization protocol.
- I learned more about C, Rust, team working and how to manage a big project.

Internship at VUI

Remote | Mar 2021 - May 2021

- I worked in the R&D team and I developed a user simulator needed for the training of a dialogue system.
- I used the user simulator to train a reinforcement learning agent for my bachelor's thesis.

EDUCATION

University of Trento (2021- expected March 2024)

Master degree in Artificial Intelligence Systems

• Current GPA: 3.84 (28.08 / 30)

University of Trento (2018 - 2021)

Bachelor degree in Computer Science

• Final grade: 110/110 Cum Laude

G.B. Brocchi high school (2013 - 2018)

Scientific high school

• Final grade 95/100

COURSES

Cyberchallenge.it

Italian training program in cybersecurity

- Topics: Reversing, Cryptography, Network Security, Pwning, Web Security
- I finished 3rd in the local final
- Our University's team finished 12th in the national final

OTHER AWARDS

- Italian swimming Championship in 100m freestyle (March 2015)
- Partecipation in the EYOF (European Youth Olympic Festival) in 2015 with the Italian National swimming team.
- Panathlon award 2014 and 2015 (for sport and school results)